<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dropbox Folder Gallery</string>
    <string name="contentDescription">content description</string>
    <string name="dbx_api_app_key">4sn6e2y4h18bvn9</string>
    <string name="client_identifier">FolderGallery/0.0.0</string>
    <string name="everywhare">Everywhere</string>
    <string name="nosubfoldershere">No sub-folders here. Go back and try again.</string>
    <string name="stop">stop</string>
    <string name="blank">blank</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome\n\nDropbox Folder Gallery quickly and efficiently shows the images in a selected folder and subfolders in your Dropbox storage. A thumbnail is stored into temporary storage, and your selected full size image are downloaded and retained in your device media storage. Note: The official Dropbox application photo menu shows all photos in all folders only. Dropbox Folder Gallery is not affiliated with Dropbox in any way.</string>
    <string name="permissons">\nPermissions\n\nWhen prompted please login to your Dropbox account. Then when prompted again please grant permission for Dropbox FolderGallery profile to have read access your Dropbox folders and files. These are needed to safely navigate your Dropox folders and files.</string>
    <string name="navigation">\nNavigation\n\nThe Play button beside the folder name starts the scan and display of image thumbnails below that folder. Click on a folder name to reveal its sub-folders. Scroll the gallery up or down and click on a image to download the full version into the Dropbox Folder Gallery folder in your device gallery storage.</string>
    <string name="dont_show_next_time">Do not show next time?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_disclaimer">DisclaimerActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">Terms\n\nPlease ensure that before using Dropbox Folder Gallery that you expressly understand and agree that your use of this application is at your sole risk and that the application is provided “as is” and “as available” without warranty of any kind, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law.\n\nOnce the applicable is available to you through your google account, you should check the application as soon as reasonably possible to ensure that it functions and performs as stated, and notify us or Provider as soon as reasonably possible if you find any errors or defect. See the Google Play Refund Policy for more information.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_accept">I accept these terms.</string>
</resources>