<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dropbox Folder Gallery</string>
    <string name="contentDescription">content description</string>
    <string name="dbx_api_app_key">4sn6e2y4h18bvn9</string>
    <string name="client_identifier">FolderGallery/0.0.0</string>
    <string name="everywhare">Everywhere</string>
    <string name="nosubfoldershere">No sub-folders here. Go back and try again.</string>
    <string name="stop">stop</string>
    <string name="blank">blank</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome\n\nDropbox Folder Gallery quickly and efficiently shows the images in a selected folder and its subfolders in your online Dropbox storage. The official Dropbox application photo provides an adequate gallery view of all photos in all folders. Please note this refined Dropbox Folder Gallery application is not affiliated with Dropbox in any way.</string>
    <string name="permissons">\nPermissions\n\nNo special Android permissions are required. On first run you will be prompted to login to your Dropbox account using a browser. Then when prompted again please grant permission for Dropbox FolderGallery profile to have read access your Dropbox folders and files. Read only access is needed to safely navigate your Dropox folders and files.</string>
    <string name="navigation">\nNavigation\n\nThe folders screen lists the folders in your dropbox top level. The Play button beside the folder name starts the scan and display of image thumbnails below that folder.  Click on a folder name to reveal its sub-folders. If a fast forward button appears please click to load more folders. The spanner icon selects administration tools. Here you can delete cache files, and disconnect your dropbox. The Gallery screen downloads small thumbnails in batches. Scroll the thumbnails up or down to see all the images. Click on a image to download the full version into the gallery storage. The image is actually placed in a special gallery album called "Dropbox Folder Gallery". Long click a thumbnail to check the image details in your dropbox storage.</string>
    <string name="dont_show_next_time">Do not show next time?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_disclaimer">DisclaimerActivity</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">Terms\n\nPlease ensure that before using Dropbox Folder Gallery that you expressly understand and agree that your use of this application is at your sole risk and that the application is provided “as is” and “as available” without warranty of any kind, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law.\n\nOnce the applicable is available to you through your google account, you should check the application as soon as reasonably possible to ensure that it functions and performs as stated, and notify us or Provider as soon as reasonably possible if you find any errors or defect. See the Google Play Refund Policy for more information.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_accept">I accept these terms.</string>
    <string name="clear_cache_files_text">Administration Options\n\nTouch clean cache files to all tempory files. Note that images will not be removed from your device gallery</string>
    <string name="disconnect_dropbox_text">Touch disconnect dropbox to end the connection to your dropbox. Restart Dropbox Folder Gallery to reconnect or choose another dropbox</string>
</resources>